<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>219th Birmingham Scout Group on 219th Birmingham Scouts</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 219th Birmingham Scout Group on 219th Birmingham Scouts</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Costs</title>
      <link>/costs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/costs/</guid>
      <description>Subs is £30 a school term and is expected to be paid at the start of the term. This is to cover the group running costs which includes:
Scout Association membership dues Meeting place rental Camping equipment storage rental Activity materials You may notice there is no mention of staff or leader costs. This is because all leaders and members of the executive committee are volunteers and do not receive any remumeration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Find Us</title>
      <link>/location/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/location/</guid>
      <description>The group meets on Tuesdays during school terms at Gospel Oak Community Centre at St Michael&amp;rsquo;s Church. The Beavers, Cubs and Scouts meet from 18:30 to 20:00. The Explorers meet from 20:15 to 21:15.
The address is:
St Michael&amp;rsquo;s Church,
17 Redstone Farm Road,
Hall Green,
Birmingham,
B28 9NU</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Join</title>
      <link>/join/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/join/</guid>
      <description>Young Person The first step to joining is to contact Raksha for Beavers, Cubs and Scouts or Skip for Explorers. Their contact details are on the home page. We will answer any questions and would appreciate if you could give us any information regarding your young person&amp;rsquo;s history. We have many young people in the group with different needs and it is better for all if these are known ahead of time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social Media</title>
      <link>/socialmedia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/socialmedia/</guid>
      <description>The group uses 2 different key methods to communicate with the carers of young people within the group. The first is the use of e-mail through Online Scout Manager, software which the group uses for handling personal data and general Scouting admin. An account should be set up as part of the joining process.
The second method is through a Facebook group. This is where we share images from camps and activities as well as news about up coming meeting changes or activities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uniform and Badges</title>
      <link>/uniform/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/uniform/</guid>
      <description>The Scouts are an uniformed organisation and so it is expected that all members of the group will wear uniform. Each section has a different jumper or shirt to wear. Uniform can be bought from the following places:
Scouts Shop The Scout Shop at Rough Close camp site Online from Rough Close Scout Shop eBay Badge Placement Diagrams Beavers Cubs Scouts Explorers </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
